Mommy Guide Inc: See you in a bit.:) excited much Markus & Stephanie.:)
BravoPup Dog Training: front row!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sandi!
Markus Schaub: Follow Sarah: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCMwT5R2rqwgRMt7ntCvTF2w
BravoPup Dog Training: Hi Lala!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: hey Markus and Sarah!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Markus!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Darn.....Sandi beat me to the front row!
Make and Do Crafts: Hi Markus, it's Diane!Your video came up in my feed! You're a star!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Hi Lala!! Hi Ellie! Hi Sandi!
Ana Zugheri: Hi 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stephanie @Sparkle Rise Thrive
Ana Zugheri: Hello ladies!!!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Hi Diane and Ana!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ana!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: I'm dancing in my chair right now....
Make and Do Crafts: Hello @Sparkle Rise Thrive
Mommy Guide Inc: And yey! Countdown has started:)
BravoPup Dog Training: Q: I throw everything I don't want to see in my 'closets and drawers' - what does that make me?? A closet hoarder?
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Everyone!!!
Caleb McDonald: Hey hey 👋🏻
BravoPup Dog Training: Hey everyone! - Sandi
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie!
Make and Do Crafts: Hi everyone!
Caleb McDonald: STEPHANIE! 😉 ✋🏻
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @BravoPup Dog Training - YESSSSSSSS!! 🙂
Ana Zugheri: I just love love love seeing y’all here and Markus!!!???? Wow! Love that he applies what we have learned
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Hi Caleb!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Diane@makeanddocrafts
Ellie Calhoun: Me too Stephanie! I've got to get music for my lives!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: all of my alarms are going off now....I set three so I wouldn't miss this today 🙂
Make and Do Crafts: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: 4 alarm clocks for me!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Caleb!
Make and Do Crafts: Yes it's Diane!
BravoPup Dog Training: its 4 am or something for Lala!!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: We can hear Sarah's mic
Ellie Calhoun: Ha ha!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Not that she would say anything inappropriate....
Caleb McDonald: That’s what she said
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Caleb McDonald ha ha ha ha
Ellie Calhoun: Is that what's called a 'hot mic'?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes and am dancing with Markus and Sara:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Markus!!!
Ana Zugheri: Hello 👋
Ana Zugheri: So excited!!! Yes!!!!
Make and Do Crafts: I love my art supplies and clutter!
Ellie Calhoun: Oh so so so many things!! Yes!
BravoPup Dog Training: YES! GET RID OF CRAP!
Ana Zugheri: I so need to hear this! Hi Sarah
Sparkle Rise Thrive: I am slowing working on becoming a minimalist...
Make and Do Crafts: Hi Marcus and Sarah!
BravoPup Dog Training: Q: I throw everything I don't want to see in my 'closets and drawers' - what does that make me?? A closet hoarder?
Sparkle Rise Thrive: I am SO glad @Caleb McDonald is here too....can't wait to see the hand puppets!
Ellie Calhoun: I'm not interested in minimalist, but certainly less than what I'm holding on to!
Ana Zugheri: Sentimental valué…i need to detach of some stuff
S❣d: Love Sarah!!! 🥰❤
Caleb McDonald: Hahaha Stephanie… we’ll what happens!!🤣🤪
Caleb McDonald: We’ll see what happens!* 🙈
Mommy Guide Inc: That's so inspiring Sarah:)
Caleb McDonald: Interview looks great MARKUS!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Clutter stresses me out but I have executive function issues because of my ADHD. So I need some strategies in how to 'don't put it down, put it away'
Ellie Calhoun: If it sparks joy! Yes!
S❣d: Nice to know who you are Markus after seeing you on Sarah's Channel
Make and Do Crafts: Q: Is there such a term as maximalist?
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi S❣d!
Caleb McDonald: Hi SAMMY!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Hey Sammy!
Make and Do Crafts: Hi @Sammy Super Star
Caleb McDonald: Hi Zoë! 👋🏻 Great to see you here!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sammy Super Star:)
Sparkle Rise Thrive: I have 1,000 pens/markers alone
Mommy Guide Inc: Small changes:)
Ellie Calhoun: Wow!
S❣d: 👋Sarah
Caleb McDonald: The Facebook Group 👉🏻 SmallChangers .com
S❣d: Hi Caleb😊
Ellie Calhoun: And then there's just disorganized and don't get around to getting things out the door that you are done with!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Q: do you feel that sometimes past/childhood trauma manifests itself in hoarding?
Mommy Guide Inc: Follow Sarah: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCMwT...
Sparkle Rise Thrive: oooooooo....I love that you are flexible and are not legalistic about minimalism
Roy W. Richardson: I am a digital hoarder. I can always buy bigger cloud drives.
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Stephanie @Sparkle Rise Thrive - Sarah's way is very inclusive. No judgment - just pure desire to help.
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Sarah!!! You are SO AMAZING!!!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Roy W. Richardson:)
Caleb McDonald: I hear ya Roy, I’m a digital hoarder too! I & 0’s don’t take up physical space which is awesome. 🙌🏻
Caleb McDonald: Book Sarah 👉🏻 SmallChanges .tv/Services
Ellie Calhoun: Q: Once a home is cluttered to an overwhelming point, what do you think is the first and best step to get started?
Roy W. Richardson: if we at least organize our stuff in storage and labeled, is it somewhat okay? I keep a lot of old cables and over the years it has come in so handy to help others.
BravoPup Dog Training: Q: Can you speak to closet hoarding? I throw everything in closets to keep it out of sight.
Ana Zugheri: So much great info
Sparkle Rise Thrive: PILES!!!!! They are the bane of my existence!! I am going to try out your timer strategy!
Roy W. Richardson: @BravoPup Dog Training yeah, me too.
Ellie Calhoun: 15 minutes... you can do anything for 15 minutes
Roy W. Richardson: @Mommy Guide Inc Hey Lala!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Ellie Calhoun soooo true!
Mommy Guide Inc: 15min of constant and intentional decluttering. Great way to not get overwhelmed:)
S❣d: I learning what looks good isn't always what makes life easy
Ellie Calhoun: Sometimes I don't get it out of the house and then I feel like I need to go thru that box again 😂😜
S❣d: throws, cushions, venetian blinds 😳
Mommy Guide Inc: Declutter first before organizing! awesome tip!
Sammy Super Star: I will never declutter macs LOL 😂
Roy W. Richardson: Also I have some stuff that at one time was very expensive but now fairly obsolete. My price doesn't want me to throw such large spending from the past away.
Mommy Guide Inc: Macs make Sammy happy:)
Ellie Calhoun: @sammy it's your collection!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: ooooooo....we are getting the dirt on @Caleb McDonald 🙂
Caleb McDonald: Hahaha 🙈
Caleb McDonald: The struggles are real
Roy W. Richardson: @Sammy Super Star start the Sammy Super Star Mac Museum.
Ellie Calhoun: I got some old macs sitting around 😂
Make and Do Crafts: I agree, getting rid of boxes/packaging is a great way to start
Mommy Guide Inc: bye bye boxes!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Caleb McDonald needs all of his boxes to build a doomsday shelter for the whole family...
Ellie Calhoun: It might be useful some day!
Sammy Super Star: LOL I think you haven’t seen my background before that’s the Mac museum @Roy W Richardson
Caleb McDonald: Minimalist Doomsday Prepper. I think that’s gonna be my YouTube channel. Great idea Stephanie!!
BravoPup Dog Training: i have a lot of closets
Caleb McDonald: A minimalist who needs boxes to save his family.
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Caleb McDonald DO IT!!! I would subscribe to that channel!
S❣d: 👐
Roy W. Richardson: @Sammy Super Star I have seen it. All those Macs in the cubbies behind you.
BravoPup Dog Training: Thank you! I know this - but ...... i dont do it!
Ellie Calhoun: If I ever have to move, I'm in trouble!
Caleb McDonald: The Walking Dead meets Maria Kondo
Caleb McDonald: Decluttering those Walkers. The struggle gets really real.
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Caleb McDonald THE WORLD NEEDS THIS KIND OF CONTENT!!!!
Ellie Calhoun: I'm inspired to start 15 minutes daily of decluttering!
Mommy Guide Inc: Function over aesthetic:) awesome.
Sammy Super Star: Q. Have anyone asked you to down size A studio with cables and gear if so I would need help lol 😆 I have every cable and I don’t need them anymore. I still have floppy disk drive cable
BravoPup Dog Training: I've thrown away a few items everyday since meeting Sarah in LEDA. Im going to tackle my closets and drawers now.
Sparkle Rise Thrive: More dirt on @Caleb McDonald - he eats all the food
Ellie Calhoun: In our town we have a Buy Nothing facebook group. Where if you don't want to throw something out you post it as a giveaway and someone else can use it- gift it
Sammy Super Star: True
Caleb McDonald: Hahaha… Stephanie, that’s FAKE NEWS!
Make and Do Crafts: Q I have boxes and boxes of old photos. Can't face getting rid of them, but they take up room. Any suggestions?
Sparkle Rise Thrive: An onion? What about a nice parfait? sorry....Shrek reference
Caleb McDonald: Backup, backup and backup! 💯
Paul Burke: That's the golden rule. I remember jesus saying that..."two is one, and one is none...OK. I'm out!" 🙂
Caleb McDonald: lol PAUL!! 👋🏻
Sparkle Rise Thrive: ITS ALWAYS THE MANS FAULT!! ALWAYS
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Paul Burke
Paul Burke: hey @Mommy Guide Inc
Sparkle Rise Thrive: HEY @Paul Burke
Paul Burke: first toss everything that's not important...inhalers....heart medication...etc
Paul Burke: hey @Sparkle Rise Thrive
Ana Zugheri: What??????
Ana Zugheri: Yes! It’s the man’s fault
Sparkle Rise Thrive: I don't have ANYTHING on my walls...painted a few years ago and didn't put anything up. So now I don't have to dust any paintings
Paul Burke: I realize having so many paintings and pictures on the walls is really distracting around the house when shooting videos too
Sparkle Rise Thrive: I should clarify, we painted the walls and never put any wall hangings or paintings or pictures up
Paul Burke: wall clutter is making the videos moer difficult to shoot
BravoPup Dog Training: @Sparkle Rise Thrive You're suppose to dust pictures on the wal???
Paul Burke: @Sparkle Rise Thrive ...i never thought about dusting pictures...but...that's true....I'm sure they do get dusty
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @BravoPup Dog Training 🙂
Ana Zugheri: We moved last year and I have a lot of bare walls…I love it 😍 I didn’t know I did. I realized I don’t have put stuff on the walls
Ana Zugheri: Lol 😂 thank you Markus for the correction lol
Ana Zugheri: 😂
BravoPup Dog Training: My mom's husband is a hoarder. I can't even go to the house anymore. 😞
Ana Zugheri: Yes vulnerability
Ellie Calhoun: Right! Great points Sarah
Sparkle Rise Thrive: ooooooo...such great advice!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Do you go on YouTube on a consistent day and time?
Mommy Guide Inc: collaboration not competition:)
Ana Zugheri: Yes
Mommy Guide Inc: whether it be recorded or livestreaming - be consistent:) thanks Sarah.
S❣d: @ Sarah do you ever feel stressed with providing content and new ideas ?? plus being a mum with all those demands ?
Paul Burke: i do that too
S❣d: constantly learning
Ellie Calhoun: 🤣real life in the home! Love 💕
Paul Burke: great mindset
Caleb McDonald: “I know where you live” 😆aka TAKEN, “we will find you, and we WILL help you.”
CasualWhiteGuy: blimey mate, ive gotta clear the mind with some top shelf chronic
Make and Do Crafts: Q Do you plan in advance?or more spontaneous?
S❣d: @Caleb I would love Sarah to come to mine for coffee..I think we would have so much to talk about
Heather Roma: Hey you two! 👋🏼
Sparkle Rise Thrive: LOOOOOOVED THIS!!!
BravoPup Dog Training: THANK YOU!
Mommy Guide Inc: That's so perfectly said Sarah.
Make and Do Crafts: Thanks Sarah and Markus!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus and Sarah!
Paul Burke: great live 🙂