Kali Co: EEEEEP!!! so excited for this!!! ❤️
BravoPup Dog Training: I'm here already! - Sandi
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Kali@ Hi @Sandi:)
Sparkle Rise Thrive: MARKUS!!! Can't wait to see you!!!
BravoPup Dog Training: Hi Lala! Hi Kali!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Hi Lala, Hi Kali, Hi Sandi!!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Markus - you are going to CRUSH this!!!
BravoPup Dog Training: hey Stephanie!!
BravoPup Dog Training: MAAARRKKUUSSS!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stephanie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yeah! This is it - Markus!
David W. Ryan: Markus!!!!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: oooooo....only 30 seconds to go!!! EXCITED!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @David W. Ryan
BravoPup Dog Training: EEEEEEEEEE!!!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: ITS TIME!!!
Julie Ulrich: Hi Markus!!
Kali Co: yay!!!!!!
Yuka Nakasone: Hi Markus
Kali Co: ❤ ❤ ❤
Yuka Nakasone: That's what I need to do.
BravoPup Dog Training: The gang is all here!!
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS!!
Kali Co: Swimming. I was NOT ready to swim when I wanted to. I did try and then I drowned and then I was too afraid to try again until I was 12, and then something clicked and i swam!
Daniel Chi: Yayyyyy!!!!!!
Live Streaming Pros: MARKUS!
Mommy Guide Inc: Markusss! Setting up! gosh didn't see the messenger thing til now!!! waah
Kali Co: i'm a great swimmer now 😌 😂
Kali Co: that would be great 🤗 some day!!
Kali Co: awe! ❤️
Sparkle Rise Thrive: LURIA!!!!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: I'll come 🏊🏻‍♀️
Kali Co: @Sarah | Small Changes heck yeah!! ❤
Live Streaming Pros: And you’re doing it!! So proud of you!
Kali Co: Markus you have TONS to share with people and talk about 🤗
Daniel Chi: I can swim from one side of the pool to the other! Granted, it’s a plastic turtle pool.
Kali Co: @Daniel Chi LOL
BravoPup Dog Training: super proud of you Markus!! You Inspire me.
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Sarah | Small Changes - maybe all of us should hop a flight to Australia and we can swim in the ocean
Sarah | Small Changes: @Daniel Chi 🤣 Still counts!
Yuka Nakasone: 😅 That's me.... I am wondering what I would say in LinkedIn Live tomorrow.
Sarah | Small Changes: @Sparkle Rise Thrive YES PLEASE!!!!!
Mark Thomas: Hey Markus
Kali Co: Streamer Swimmer party!
Julie Ulrich: you're doing great Markus!!!
Mark Thomas: What’s on your cap?
Sarah | Small Changes: Q: Do they have beaches in Switzerland?
BravoPup Dog Training: uh oh. Markus just called me out. I'm next!!
Kali Co: feline fetus!
Yuka Nakasone: OH Kali's????? Wow
Kali Co: feline fetus is a superhero
Kali Co: woah i'm official!!! a wrench!!! heck yeah!!! ❤
Sarah | Small Changes: YES SANDI!!!
Julie Ulrich: Go Sandi!!
Yuka Nakasone: And a beautiful bridge that you streamed from
Kali Co: yay!!!!! LALA!!!!!
Mark Thomas: Of course, how can I forget Kali’s emotional response when she opened it 🥰
Yuka Nakasone: Hey LALA!!!
BravoPup Dog Training: LaLa!!!
Julie Ulrich: Hi Lala!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: Hi lala!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: LALA 🎉
Kali Co: awe ❤ ❤ @Mark Thomas
Live Streaming Pros: LALA!!!
CK's Antics: hey Markus and Lala!!
Paul Burke: hey Markus! Hey Lala!
David W. Ryan: Hi LALA
Kali Co: Which camera is lala using??
CK's Antics: Great job!
BravoPup Dog Training: where the hell is John Pullum?
David W. Ryan: This is fun!
Yuka Nakasone: Yes, we are so proud. I am curious where this will go!
CK's Antics: Lala had a R2D2!!
Kali Co: ohhhhh i was like "this is a different angle than i'm used to with lala" hahaha
Julie Ulrich: I love your R2D2 Lala!
CK's Antics: *has
Paul Burke: OOOO......rockin the kali cap
Kali Co: @Paul Burke ❤
Kali Co: hahahahaha the last leg!
Yuka Nakasone: I don't have any spare....
Kali Co: famous last words 😂
CK's Antics: Haha!! love it lala!! backup to the backup! You're prepared
Yuka Nakasone: Yes, because you are a star, Markus.
Mark Thomas: Lala looks like she’s ready to sing
Paul Burke: watching the high energy of Lala and the mellow of Markus is the best
Cat Mulvihill: Hey @Markus Schaub 👋 Excited to see you live!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Paul Burke YES!!!!
CK's Antics: oh nice!! learning as you stream
Julie Ulrich: Markus is an ecamm expert!
David W. Ryan: yes!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: whoo hoo!!!! you did it Markus!
Kali Co: hahahaha that's much better!
CK's Antics: hurray!! we did it!! go team
Kali Co: #techonthefly
Yuka Nakasone: wow....
Paul Burke: Welcome to Lala Coaching
Mark Thomas: That was cool 😎
Yuka Nakasone: I need Lala Coaching
Sarah | Small Changes: #EverythingGoesWrongWhenYoureLive
David W. Ryan: lol!
Live Streaming Pros: Oh the mute button. 😳
SuzanCz: Hi all!
SuzanCz: Lala - you aren't lagging at this end.
Mark Thomas: No lagging here
Sarah | Small Changes: You look and sound great Lala
CK's Antics: love the conversation! tech will get you eventually and it's not just a one time thing...just be prepared and stream on!
Yuka Nakasone: I wasn't ready to raise a child but I had to do it.... she wouldn't wait. 😆
Live Streaming Pros: That’s just the lower quality signal you’re getting as a guest Lala - your good!
Sarah | Small Changes: YES!!!
Live Streaming Pros: lol @yuka
Kali Co: that's a good commitment 🤗
Paul Burke: 4 times a week!? Fantastic!
SuzanCz: good start. Do it four times and then see how you feel about it.
BravoPup Dog Training: getting my calendar out! (no post its Stephanie!)
Mark Thomas: Invite Kali to tell the story about your cap
SuzanCz: @Paul Burke causing trouble. no surprise.
Sara S: Markus!! I’m late. I was working.
Julie Ulrich: Every Thursday is Markus Thursday!
Cat Mulvihill: Give it longer than you think you need 😉
Sarah | Small Changes: Do we all get a turn to come on?
Kali Co: ❤
Paul Burke: @SuzanCz ....an honest mistake 😏
Kali Co: @Sarah | Small Changes i second this question!
Kali Co: 😲 what!!!
SuzanCz: @Paul Burke Ha! 😉
CK's Antics: Dang, Kali has a wrench 🔧 already!!
SuzanCz: Ooooh - Sarah would make a great guest!
Kali Co: @CK's Antics don't you forget it 😎
Kali Co: i'll have to change with the shipping 😕
Paul Burke: Lala's origin story!!
Live Streaming Pros: lol I missed page 2
Cat Mulvihill: 8 years!? Wow
Andy Halper: All here for you Markus!
Live Streaming Pros: ❤️❤️❤️
Yuka Nakasone: This gives me courage to go live tomorrow on LinkedIn.
Sparkle Rise Thrive: 4 hours?!?!?!? That sounds like a @Paul Burke stream 🙂
Live Streaming Pros: 4 hours with echo that’s amazing hahahahahaaa
Sarah | Small Changes: Did anyone else watch Luria @Live Streaming Pros as Calli and now you confuse yourself with @Kali Co 🤣
Paul Burke: I'd love to see Markus and Lala and two cops interogating something....Good cop and Super Mellow Cop
Live Streaming Pros: lol @sarah - yeah it’s confusing lol
Paul Burke: @Sparkle Rise Thrive ...but I don't keep everyone for 4 hours 🤣😂
Kali Co: @Sarah | Small Changes LOL
Yuka Nakasone: Oh.... thank you...
Live Streaming Pros: lol Paul
Yuka Nakasone: Absolutely.
Paul Burke: Lala is good Cop.... Markus is super mellow cop (SMC)
Live Streaming Pros: Just wear pants. #Boundaries
Yuka Nakasone: You are lovely
CK's Antics: yes!! R2D2!!!!
Yuka Nakasone: 😄
Sarah | Small Changes: Lala can we do some geeky crafting?
Paul Burke: @Live Streaming Pros ....are you creating a wednesday video called Boundary Tips: Power of Pants
BravoPup Dog Training: am I the only one who hasn't seen Star Wars?
Paul Burke: @BravoPup Dog Training ...any of them?
Sarah | Small Changes: @BravoPup Dog Training WHAT?!
BravoPup Dog Training: i fell asleep during the first one and then it was over. No.
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Paul Burke now I have the Phineas and Ferb song....SIMP....squirrels in my pants....
Live Streaming Pros: @paul stop telling everyone our content plan!!!
Kali Co: that's awesome! ❤
David W. Ryan: Geeky Crafting sounds fun
Kali Co: @Live Streaming Pros LOL
Paul Burke: @Live Streaming Pros ..sorry....I'm so excited about your upcoming Clothing While Livestreaming SERIES
Paul Burke: @Sparkle Rise Thrive ....hahaha 🙂
Sarah | Small Changes: @Paul Burke please tell me thats stage 1 content 🤣
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Paul Burke what is Stage 2 content?
Paul Burke: @Sarah | Small Changes ...it's the content people want 😂🤣
Sparkle Rise Thrive: I can hear him
Cat Mulvihill: I can hear you both
CK's Antics: I've got your audio Markua
BravoPup Dog Training: audio is fine
Live Streaming Pros: Markus has audio
David W. Ryan: audio is fine for us
CK's Antics: Your audio is fine, it's lala
Live Streaming Pros: Lala leave and come back
Sarah | Small Changes: we can hear you both ❤️
Sara S: I hear Markus
SuzanCz: Everything sounds fine here
Kali Co: lala is better now
Paul Burke: @Markus Schaub ....rollin solo!
Live Streaming Pros: Did your Bluetooth earbuds die?
CK's Antics: you're not alone, we are here with you!
Paul Burke: @Live Streaming Pros ...thats strange...you always swear by bluetooth. That's like LSP 101....always use bluetooth...don't trust cables
CK's Antics: keep moving her up, just line up the shoulders
Sarah | Small Changes: We can all come on and tell you our live stream fails 🤣
SuzanCz: Ahhh... @Sarah | Small Changes So it's a comedy show!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Live Streaming Pros Luria LOVES bluetooth headphones. 🙂
Live Streaming Pros: That does sound like me @paul
Live Streaming Pros: Sorry Lala - I’m on mobile I couldn’t see your wires hahaha
Paul Burke: @Sparkle Rise Thrive ....I'm not sure what stage 2 will be. 😊🤔
Live Streaming Pros: If I come on to tell my live stream issues you’ll need 16 hours
Paul Burke: and if you dislike the guest....just don't let them back in
Sarah | Small Changes: @Paul Burke 🤣
SuzanCz: So Markus.... how are you feeling about this experience? You're doing fabulous!
Kali Co: LOL
Kali Co: noted 😂😂😂😂
Sarah | Small Changes: I'll remember that for when I come on 🤣
Live Streaming Pros: #ProTip 🤣
SuzanCz: @Paul Burke Start with: I"m sorry. I can't hear you! The doors right there.... don't let it hit you...
Cat Mulvihill: Pro Tip from a Pro
Sarah | Small Changes: @SuzanCz Mellow Cop turns Bad 🤣
Paul Burke: @SuzanCz 🤣😂
Sparkle Rise Thrive: @Sarah | Small Changes 🙂 ha ha ha!
Kali Co: i take my mod job seriously and i am here to whoop a**
Kali Co: LOL
Sarah | Small Changes: Lala tell us a craft fail
Paul Burke: Where ISN'T kali a mod 😂
Kali Co: LOL
SuzanCz: @Kali Co is the backend bouncer
Sarah | Small Changes: @Paul Burke I thought that said " When ISNT Kali in a mood... and I was like... Harsh 🤣
Kali Co: @SuzanCz 😂😂😂
Kali Co: @Sarah | Small Changes i mean, that too 😂😂😂😂
Kali Co: woah! that is awesome lala!!!
Yuka Nakasone: OH MY GOD
Sarah | Small Changes: PC, well thats your problem 🤣
Yuka Nakasone: Great.
Yuka Nakasone: I need Lala Coaching
Yuka Nakasone: Yeeesss!!
Cat Mulvihill: Yes, Lala, it's all about taking action
Yuka Nakasone: OK, I will do it. Tomorrow. I promise.
Sarah | Small Changes: YASS @Yuka Nakasone 🎉
Kali Co: yes!! live streaming definitely helps us learn more about ourselves i think
Yuka Nakasone: 💗
Paul Burke: @Sarah | Small Changes ...you're onto me. I'm a very harsh person
Kali Co: you are both inspirations ❤
SuzanCz: It's a love fest! And rightly so
Paul Burke: @Markus Schaub ...lets be honest...few people can pull off yellow...it's working for you
Yuka Nakasone: Yes, I will let y ou know.
Kali Co: Q who will be your next guest?
Kali Co: sorry wait that's a lot of pressure
Paul Burke: yeah @Markus Schaub ..who is your next guest?
Paul Burke: no @Kali Co ...keep that pressure on
CK's Antics: Great job @Markus
Kali Co: i'll grab it!
Sara S: I have to go back to work. Bye all!
SuzanCz: @Paul Burke Truth! So few people can pull it off. It's working for Markus. I think the hat pulls it together!
Kali Co: Sarah's link: https://www.youtube.com/c/SmallChangesTV
Mark Thomas: Not unless you’re trying to volunteer @kali
Kali Co: @Paul Burke LOL
Kali Co: @Sara S bye!!! ❤
CK's Antics: @Kali crushing the mod duties
Kali Co: @Mark Thomas i'd come on 100000000%
Sarah | Small Changes: KALI NEXT!!!!
SuzanCz: Is this your vision, Markus? To do all interviews?
Kali Co: i volunteer!
Mark Thomas: ❤️
CK's Antics: @Kali will mod her own interview
Yuka Nakasone: Let's count beer, Markus.
Kali Co: @CK's Antics damn right
Sarah | Small Changes: First time I've ever hand a wrench.... physical or virtual 🤣
SuzanCz: Yay @Kali Co!
Kali Co: @Sarah | Small Changes LOL
Kali Co: 😂😂😂😂
Sarah | Small Changes: @Kali Co Should let us all MOD for her 🤣
Kali Co: hahahha pjs RULE
SuzanCz: @Sarah | Small Changes Are you feeling the power of the 🔧?
David W. Ryan: Pajama Jam with Markus!
Kali Co: @Sarah | Small Changes 😂😂😂😂
Kali Co: PaJAMa
Paul Burke: great job @Markus Schaub
BravoPup Dog Training: Thank you!!!
SuzanCz: Oh -- is that another theme? We have to wear our pajamas if we're on Markus's show?
Sarah | Small Changes: I'll probably go mad with power 😈
SuzanCz: PajamaJam
Sarah | Small Changes: You did amazing Markus ❤️