Cheryl French: Waiting impatiently for the Markus and Yuko Show! 😁
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone! Wide awake now excitedly waiting foe today’s stream:)
Sarah | Small Changes: HI Cheryl and Lala, I've been missing you both!
Sara S: Made it!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! Sara@smallchanges - Hi!
Sammy Super Star: Hey
Sammy Super Star: What is up
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: YUKA!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Cheryl French and @ Tracey Akitt
Sammy Super Star: lol your guests don’t dance really
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey @Sammy Super Star!
Sammy Super Star: lol I’m dancing
Sammy Super Star: Hey @Mommy Guide Inc
Sara S: Love the music!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus & Yuka!
Sammy Super Star: 💃🕺💃🕺💃
Sammy Super Star: Hope everyone is doing well
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sara!
Ellie Calhoun: Markus!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi @Ellie!
Ellie Calhoun: Yuka good to see you!
BravoPup Dog Training: Hi!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @ Sandi! Yes Yuka! In the Phil it brings good luck
Ellie Calhoun: hi lala! @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: So almost all business eatabilshments have them to bring good luck
Sarah | Small Changes: Oh I love those cats!
Sammy Super Star: That’s right lol
BravoPup Dog Training: Hi @ Lala!
Sammy Super Star: Cats are the best right?! @Sarah | Small Changes
Sarah | Small Changes: YASS #TeamCat 🙌🏻
Cheryl French: Here in Sweden they count floors of a building differently than we do in the States. It’s really confusing!
Cheryl French: Yes
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh there is a 0 floor
Cheryl French: Yes, the ground floor counts as first floor in US. But in Sweden the ground floor is zero!
Cheryl French: Very confusing!
Sara S: In IS it’s ground floor
Ellie Calhoun: in some places here now they also have G for ground or L for lobby
Sara S: *US
Paul Burke: So @Markus Schaub ...you're always walking around on zero floor?
Paul Burke: Zero Floor would be a good name for a book or movie
Sammy Super Star: I have never traveled out of the us before so I know US
Cheryl French: Paul Burke 🤣
Sarah | Small Changes: Q: Yuka, can you talk about walking while eating in Japan... is it a no no ?🙅🏻‍♀️
Paul Burke: @Sammy Super Star ...you've never traveled outside the US because you're a wanted man everywhere, correct? For your Macbook smuggling crimes
Sara S: Then there are Harry Potter ½ floors
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Paul Burke!
Cheryl French: Oh dear, were they “call girls”?
Paul Burke: hi @Mommy Guide Inc 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls dont forget to smash the “thumbs up” button:)
Paul Burke: @Markus Schaub ....just one of your dozens of prostitution stories 😂
BravoPup Dog Training: that's funny!
Sammy Super Star: No @Paul Burke I’m not wanted…
Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus😀
Ellie Calhoun: I never thought of that - that the website of a company would look differently in another country
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi@ Communication Social Media Livestreaming
Cheryl French: Have a recognizable brand?
Paul Burke: I remember walking by the McDonalds in Ireland and pretty amazed at the tech inside. This place has beautiful countryside and sophsitcated McDonalds? I'm moving!
Cheryl French: Oh, yes, the instructions for IKEA products are always just pictures instead of words!
Ellie Calhoun: instructions are in pictures
Cheryl French: Yeah, one could say that IKEA instructions are “universally confusing” 🤣
David W. Ryan: I speak IKEA.
John Pullum: When my wife first came to the USA for a vacation with me she kept asking to go to 7 Eleven. I didn’t know why she wanted to go so bad. After we went she was confused why there wasn’t bento boxes. :)
David W. Ryan: oh no!
Sara S: Not hallal!
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh pork is not eaten in arabic countries.
Sara S: @Cheryl French I solve that by never reading directions
Cheryl French: @Sara S hahaha
Ellie Calhoun: woah
Paul Burke: @John Pullum ....wow.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @David W. Ryan and @John Pullum 🙂
David W. Ryan: Chevrolet tried to sell their car called "Nova" in Mexico but no va means "doesn't go" in Spanish
Sara S: Oh! And Chinese has so many similar sounding words!
Sarah | Small Changes: @Paul Burke We call it Maccas 😉
Cheryl French: @David W. Ryan yeah I heard about that. Hasn’t there also been a car name that was really offensive in another language?
Ana Zugheri: Hi! so glad I catch ya'l live...my internet is acting up. So I may not stay long but will definately do the replay
Ana Zugheri: I am thinking about to start doing Spanish videos
Ellie Calhoun: more simple when you only speak one language and you are small 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ana Zugheri 🙂
Ana Zugheri: Right!
Paul Burke: @Sarah | Small Changes ...you guys Australia-inize all the words!
Ana Zugheri: Ellie you are so right.
Ana Zugheri: Si señora, hablo español.
Ana Zugheri: How long have you been in Spain?
Paul Burke: walking and eating isn't ok in Japan? Oh no! What about driving and eating? I'd be kicked out.
austinator888: hey
Paul Burke: @austinator888 ...can you make us a sandwich
austinator888: lol, sure @Paul Burke
Ana Zugheri: I started following Yokoi Kenji, learning so much from him about the Japanese culture. So reach and disciplined. Was it a culture shock for you to move to Spain?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @austinator888:)
austinator888: I don't eat food on the streets
austinator888: hey Lala @Mommy Guide Inc
Ellie Calhoun: keeps you from overeating too much I suppose. When people eat when they are walking (and driving @Paul) they end up eating all the time!
Ana Zugheri: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc love to find you with all of our friends!
Ana Zugheri: LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed @Ana.:) It’s a joy to be with you all here with Markus & Yuka. This is a very interesting topic.:)
Ana Zugheri: Oh! gosh...you wouldn't survive in Mexico...we scream to talk!!!!!
Ellie Calhoun: lol 🤣
Ana Zugheri: wow!!! that is self control
Paul Burke: hahaha.... @Ana Zugheri ...people ask me, "am I angry?"...and I respond, "no, I'm just loud"
Ana Zugheri: lol
Ana Zugheri: co-exist!!! love it
Ana Zugheri: I am married to an Italian guy and we first got married there was a big clash of culture.
Ellie Calhoun: fascinating!
Sara S: What language is used in government?
Sleep for the Soul: Hi Yuka and Markus!!!
Paul Burke: you're such a casual interviewer @Markus Schaub ...it's a fun style
Ellie Calhoun: My brother lived in Spain for 10 years. it was very difficult for him and I don't think he ever managed to be accepted.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Kristina @Sleep for the Soul
Sleep for the Soul: Look at you now Yuka!!!
Paul Burke: Sorry...maybe I missed it....but why is "no" so taboo?
Ellie Calhoun: saying no without saying no is useful when dealing with children!😅
Sleep for the Soul: @ Mommy Guide Inc HI LALA!!!!!!
Sleep for the Soul: Are many Americans retiring in Spain?
Ellie Calhoun: He was in Basque Country, might be more difficult there
Sara S: British are the best! Very subtle
Ana Zugheri: wow!
Sara S: The French are snobbish about their language
Ana Zugheri: I get that....I am from mexico and there are a lot of people in Texas that are from south america and they call all Hispanic people Mexicans.
Ana Zugheri: It does not bother me that much, but I know some people that get really upset. At the end of the day I just say...call me human LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed it took me forever to buy a weighing scale un Nice. They couldnt understand me.
Sarah | Small Changes: I learnt everything I know about Japanese culture from Studio Ghibli 🤣🙈
Sara S: Same in China- not losing face is very important
Sara S: Can you talk at about backstage and frontstage (public facing) ?
Mark Thomas: It’s the same in the Middle East. Saying no is seen as an insult
Ellie Calhoun: can't understand the subtleties
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Mark Thomas:)
Sarah | Small Changes: I gotta go... but it was so lovely to see you both ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Ive been to Kyoto.:) the old capital right?
Tracey Akitt: Hey, so excited to see you both - sorry to be joining so late!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Sarah!
Ellie Calhoun: wow, it would be so difficult to live like that!
Mommy Guide Inc: The Japanese people are very kind. We got lost and they walked alongside us and not just give us directions.
Ellie Calhoun: this has been great! Thanks Markus and Yuka!
Ana Zugheri: LOL It is confusing.
Mommy Guide Inc: Dont forget to like this stream:)
Ana Zugheri: Thank you guys!
John Pullum: Thank you Yuka and Markus!
Sara S: Like the chat!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you Markus & Yuka!
Ellie Calhoun: 🥰
Mark Thomas: I missed the beer
David W. Ryan: Thanks Yuka and Markus!
John Pullum: I live in a Japanese and American house so I deal with the cultural issues daily.