BravoPup Dog Training: Front row.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Marcus!!!
Ellie Calhoun: In the front with you!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Markus!!!
Andy Halper: FUN FUN FUN!
Tech Troublemaker: Show Time!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Markus!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Stephanie!!
John Pullum: FUN FUN FUN!!!
BravoPup Dog Training: Stephanie looks extra beautiful!
Andy Halper: never simmer down!
Sarah | Small Changes: STEPHANIE, MARKUS!!!!
Andy Halper: NEVER hide yourself away!
Ellie Calhoun: It's ok to be you!
Tech Troublemaker: Edutainment
Tech Troublemaker: glitter glue might be easier and quicker. 😛
Andy Halper: bring your personality IS your content!
Tech Troublemaker: If you are having fun, it is usually contagious and others stick around to watch.
Andy Halper: SERIOUS FUN!
Ellie Calhoun: Energetic! It picks people up!
Andy Halper: Boredom Prevention thy name is Stephanie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus and Stephanie!
Ejnar Riis Hansen: Hello to everyone here😀👋
Make and Do Crafts: Hi Marcus and Stephanie. Hello everyone!
Cheryl French: Hey Markus and Stephanie!
Ellie Calhoun: It's a learning journey!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone! Pls dont’t forget to hit the 👍 button.;)
Sarah | Small Changes: i feel the same way!
Sarah | Small Changes: more LEDA!!!!!!
Andy Halper: FABULOUS!
Ellie Calhoun: Love that!
Sarah | Small Changes: Your the best Steph 🤣
Cheryl French: Hilarious 😂
BravoPup Dog Training: LOL!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Stephanie your livestreams are always so much fun.:)
Sammy Super Star: Like the new background Markus
Ejnar Riis Hansen: Hey Sammy 👋😀
Sarah | Small Changes: I say things many many times over for my recorded content
Sarah | Small Changes: then I make a blooper video 🤣
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sammy! I agree lovin’ Matkus new background:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Stephanie you bring that- fun short and concise videos.:)
Andy Halper: Look at all the fans that the 2 of you have!
Andy Halper: You're both so freak-n inspiring!
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.facebook.com/groups/onlinevideomastermindgroup/?ref=share
Ana Zugheri: Hello 👋
Andy Halper: ANA!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Sammy Super Star
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Next LEDA- Live Everyday In April/August will be next year - highly and absolutely recommend it!
BravoPup Dog Training: my brain is very good at that (making excuses)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy@Tech Troublemaker!
Ana Zugheri: Hey 👋 Andy! Lala! Sammy! All my favorite people ⭐️
BravoPup Dog Training: HI Ana!
Ellie Calhoun: And sometimes your videos aren't as bad as you think they are! Just start!
Sarah | Small Changes: You can just un-list the videos... then you keep the views 😉
Ellie Calhoun: Also I've learned that if you schedule and announce it then you have to do it!
Mommy Guide Inc: A great community to walk alongside us is awesome! Thanks for sharing that Stephanie:)
Make and Do Crafts: I’ve privated loads of early videos! They are fun to keep though
Andy Halper: This is a fantastic interview, so helpful. Well done both of you!
Ellie Calhoun: MyBodyWorks thanks!
Sarah | Small Changes: https://www.facebook.com/MyBodyWorks
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sarah@small changes! Hi Sandy@Bravo Pup!
Ellie Calhoun: Thanks @sarah!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ellie!
Ana Zugheri: Ellie’s videos soooo good 👍
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala!
BravoPup Dog Training: 👋 Lala!
Caleb McDonald: Markus!! Stephanie!! 👋🏻
Andy Halper: I did my first FB Live stream last week, lots of viewers and comments. I thought, "I'll never do that again!" You've changed my mind ... thank you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Diabe @MakeandDoCrafts!
Cheryl French: People actually like you more when you are not perfect!
Ellie Calhoun: Go Andy!
Make and Do Crafts: Hi Lala
Cheryl French: Nobody likes perfect people!
Ana Zugheri: Andy, you are a natural on camera 📷
Andy Halper: ABSOLUTELY!
Cheryl French: Being approachable is more important.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Andy and @Cheryl!
Cheryl French: Hi Lala!
Andy Halper: LALA!!!!
Ellie Calhoun: "Internet is Pretty big" ha ha! Understatement big time!🤣
Mommy Guide Inc: Put a Q before your questions and go ahead and ask them. Again dont forget to like this video:)
Ellie Calhoun: Q Stephanie - are you going to monetize your YouTube or is it just a way to be seen so people will work with you? And how can someone work with you?
John Pullum: Get the book The One Thing or Essentialism. You'll get a lot out of it.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @John!
John Pullum: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh the perfect balance between being a consumer and a creator - that’s a nice advice. Create a time limit. Awesome!
John Pullum: They are 2 books. The One Thing and Essentialism are about the same topic, but different ways of looking at it. It's about focusing on the main one thing you want to do first.
Ana Zugheri: I love the one thing book!
Ellie Calhoun: What's that saying? "Man chase two rabbits, man catch none"
Caleb McDonald: Yeah I don’t understand why Instagram is like that. Considering it’s Facebook owned, don’t know why they don’t open it up or allow live streaming from software/external cameras.
Ellie Calhoun: 😂
Ellie Calhoun: You are like my daughter, both energy and catching rabbits 😂
Coffee Talk & Tech: Hello Markus and Stephanie.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi John Ryan @Coffee Talk & Tech!
Coffee Talk & Tech: HIII!!! LALA
Coffee Talk & Tech: Time is always the big factor.
Ellie Calhoun: What about your business, how do you work with people, one on one?
Mommy Guide Inc: So correlation doesn’t always convert to realisation in terms of algorithm.:) Repurposing content - awesome!
BravoPup Dog Training: TikTok is super addictive.
Coffee Talk & Tech: @Mommy Guide Inc fact
Mommy Guide Inc: @Sandi you are crushing TikTok!
Coffee Talk & Tech: Its not dumb its fun...breaks up the hard work your doing
BravoPup Dog Training: @Mommy Guide Inc - Thank you!!
Sarah | Small Changes: Oh Steph that would be a nightmare in my house!
Caleb McDonald: Buttons 🙌🏻 ! 🚨
Ellie Calhoun: Sandi is killing it!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oooh the last time we were in the US there was this button from Staples that is similar. My daughter liked it so much we had to buy it!
Sarah | Small Changes: My kids would be pressing them constantly
BravoPup Dog Training: i have a button that swears!
Sarah | Small Changes: How do I get Dyson to sponsor us?
Nourish Hive: Hi Marcus!
Sarah | Small Changes: send it to me!!!!
Caleb McDonald: Hoverboard AND Dyson??? I think you’ve come up with a next level clean with me genre!
Ellie Calhoun: Do you gain a lot of clients thru social media?
Sarah | Small Changes: YT shorts could be your JAM!!
Coffee Talk & Tech: shorts are ok for driving your long content
Mommy Guide Inc: Nice name for your business Stephanie - SparkleRiseThrive that incorporates your personality with your goals.:) super nice!
Sarah | Small Changes: You can curate your YT home page to have a seperate line for shorts
Sarah | Small Changes: you can also bring them over from TikTok
Mommy Guide Inc: There is a different shelf for your shortd on your YT channel
Mommy Guide Inc: Ive made several to support my long content
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes YT also gives notif for your shorts
Caleb McDonald: You don’t get strikes, they just can claim your $$$ from that video alone
Sarah | Small Changes: If you are going to try TikTok may as well repurpose the content
Caleb McDonald: 🩳 are great, they are a must for all 👕
austinator: hey Markus
austinator: hey Stephanie
Coffee Talk & Tech: don't do shorts cause its easier and fast...Your long content should be king. And making long content is hard to make
Mommy Guide Inc: Just several hundred views but it did give me new subscribers
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree @CoffeeTalk&Tech longer and really thought of content is king!
Sarah | Small Changes: I think that there is something to be learnt from the young peeps on tiktok who post multiple times a day perfect or not ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Note to self - “don’t over think things!”
Mommy Guide Inc: https://sparklerisethrive.com/
Ellie Calhoun: You only need to reach the one person who needs to hear your message!
Sarah | Small Changes: Some of my biggest videos it was months before it took off
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed @Ellie! There is an audience for us out there so we just need to create content. Go out there.:)
Caleb McDonald: The problem with numbers is it’s human nature to NEVER be satisfied. We want 1K sub/view, we get 5K, then 10K, 1M & we’re still wanting more… PewDiePie is; 110M subs & he’s still always wanting more.
Ellie Calhoun: It's the adrenaline rush of getting higher #'s
Mommy Guide Inc: The Unicorn headband - you rock in those Stephanie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Field of Dreams - build it and they will come. Love that!
Ellie Calhoun: Love 💕
Caleb McDonald: That’s a great photo!
Sarah | Small Changes: i love it!!!!!!
Make and Do Crafts: Love it
Caleb McDonald: When will that be on Instagram?
Mommy Guide Inc: That photo is awesome! Would love to create a scrapbook layout of it!
Sarah | Small Changes: I kicked him out
Caleb McDonald: You could use that photo for your business; letting your sparkle thrive/roar in the mist of the judgement of the world 💯
BravoPup Dog Training: Thank you both!
Ellie Calhoun: Great to see you both!
Make and Do Crafts: Thank you both
Sarah | Small Changes: so fun to hang out with you both